Guide to the Donohoe Kelly & Co. Records, 1863-1917 JL002
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series B. General Account Books
  - Exchange on London, Dec 1887-June 1888
  - Blank Drafts, Jan 1905-Oct 1906
  - Blank Drafts Duplicates, Jan 1900-April 1906 (Volume 474)
  - Chicago Drafts, Sept 1904-Oct 1905
  - Chicago Drafts, Oct 1905-Sept 1906
  - Paris Drafts (Comptoir Nat'l), August 1898
  - Paris Drafts (Comptoir Nat'l), May 1902-Dec 1905
  - Paris Drafts (Andre, Neuflize & Cie), Jan 1892-Sept 1894 (Volume 475)
  - Dublin Drafts (Bank of Ireland, June 1898-Oct 1898
  - Drafts on Dublin, August 1905-Dec 1905
  - Drafts on Dublin, Dec 1905-Feb 1906
  - Drafts on Dublin, April 1891-Nov 1898
  - Drafts: Third National Bank, Boston, Nov 1898-Aug 1905 (Volume 476)
  - Drafts: New York, Mar 1894-Jan 1896
  - Drafts, May 1891-April 1894
  - Clearing House Check Stub Book, June-Aug 1910 (Volume 477)
  - Clearing House Check Stub Book, Aug-Oct 1910 (Volume 478)
  - Clearing House Check Stub Book, Oct 1910-Jan 1911 (Volume 479)
  - Clearing House Check Stub Book, Jan-May 1911 (Volume 480)
  - Clearing House Check Stub Book, May-Sept 1911 (Volume 481)
  - Clearing House Check Stub Book, Sept 1911-Feb 1912 (Volume 482)
  - Clearing House Check Stub Book, Feb-June 1912 (Volume 483)
  - Clearing House Check Stub Book, June-Nov 1912 (Volume 484)
  - Clearing House Check Stub Book, Nov 1912-Mar 1913 (Volume 485)
  - Clearing House Check Stub Book, Mar-August 1913 (Volume 486)
  - Check Stubs, May-Dec 1906 (Volume 487)
  - Check Stubs, June-Nov 1907 (Volume 488)
  - Check Stubs, Nov 1907-May 1908 (Volume 489)
  - Check Stubs, May-Dec 1908 (Volume 490)
  - Check Proof, Sept 1905-Oct 1906 (Volume 491)
  - Check Proof, Nov 1906-June 1908 (Volume 492)
  - Check Proof, June 1908-Jan 1910 (Volume 493)
  - Check Proof, Jan 1910-Sept 1911 (Volume 494)
  - Dividend Checks, March 1894-Sept 1897 (Volume 495)
  - Dividend Checks, Sept 1897-March 1900
  - Dividend Checks, Sept 1903-July 1907
  - Cashier's Checks, Dec 1908-June 1909
  - Cashier's Checks, June 1909-Jan 1910
  - Cashier's Checks, Jan-July 1910
  - Cashier's Checks, July 1910-Jan 1911
  - Cashier's Checks, Jan-June 1911
  - Cashier's Checks, Dec 1911-April 1912
  - Cashier's Checks, April-Sept 1912
  - Drafts: Franz Herm, Abbes & Co., 1893-1894 (Volume 496)
  - Drafts paid for account of Schulz & Ruckgaber, 1906
  - Go Backs-Clearing House, June 1905-April 1906
  - City Front Collections, Sept 1905-May 1906
  - City Collections, May-Nov 1906
  - Special Accounts and Deposits for Collection, May 1906
  - Ledger for Special Accounts, May 1906
  - Special Clearing House Checks, May 1906
  - Accounts Current, 1902-1906 (Volume 497)
  - Interest, 1901 (Volume 498)
  - Interest, 1902 (Volume 499)
  - Interest, 1903-1905 (Volume 500)
  - Interest, 1906-1907 (Volume 501)
  - Interest, 1908-1909 (Volume 502)
  - Interest, 1911 (Volume 503)
  - Balance Sheet (A-E), Jan 1892 (Volume 504)
  - (A-E), Feb 1892 (Volume 505)
  - (A-E), March 1892 (Volume 506)
  - (A-E), May 1892 (Volume 507)
  - (A-E), June 1892 (Volume 508)
  - (A-E), July 1892 (Volume 509)
  - (A-E), August 1892 (Volume 510)
  - (A-E), Sept 1892 (Volume 511)
  - (A-E), Oct 1892 (Volume 512)
  - (A-E), Dec 1892 (Volume 513)
  - (F-Mc), Oct 1896 (Volume 514)
  - (F-Mc), Oct 1897 (Volume 515)
  - (A-E), Jan 1902 (Volume 516)
  - (A-E), Feb 1902 (Volume 517)
  - (A-E), March 1902 (Volume 518)
  - (A-E), April 1902 (Volume 519)
  - (A-E), May 1902 (Volume 520)
  - (A-E), June 1902 (Volume 521)
  - (A-E), July 1902 (Volume 522)
  - (A-E), August 1902 (Volume 523)
  - (A-E), Sept 1902 (Volume 524)
  - (A-E), Oct 1902 (Volume 525)
  - (A-E), Nov 1902 (Volume 526)
  - (A-E), Dec 1902 (Volume 527)
  - (A-E), Jan 1903 (Volume 528)
  - (A-E), Feb 1903 (Volume 529)
  - (A-E), March 1903 (Volume 530)
  - (A-E), April 1903 (Volume 531)
  - (A-E), May 1903 (Volume 532)
  - (A-E), June 1903 (Volume 533)
  - (A-E), July 1903 (Volume 534)
  - (A-E), August 1903 (Volume 535)
  - (A-E), Sept 1903 (Volume 536)
  - (A-E), Oct 1903 (Volume 537)
  - (A-E), Nov 1903 (Volume 538)
  - (A-E), Dec 1903 (Volume 539)
  - Balance Sheet (A-E), Jan 1904 (Volume 540)
  - (F-M), Jan 1904 (Volume 541)
  - (N-Z), Jan 1904 (Volume 542)
  - (A-E), Feb 1904 (Volume 543)
  - (F-M), Feb 1904 (Volume 544)
  - (N-Z), Feb 1904 (Volume 545)
  - (A-E), Mar 1904 (Volume 546)
  - (F-M), Mar 1904 (Volume 547)
  - (N-Z), Mar 1904 (Volume 548)
  - (A-E), April 1904 (Volume 549)
  - (F-M), April 1904 (Volume 550)
  - (N-Z), April 1904 (Volume 551)
  - (A-E), May 1904 (Volume 552)
  - (F-M), May 1904 (Volume 553)
  - (N-Z), May 1904 (Volume 554)
  - (A-E), June 1904 (Volume 555)
  - (F-M), June 1904 (Volume 556)
  - (N-Z), June 1904 (Volume 557)
  - (A-E), July 1904 (Volume 558)
  - (F-M), July 1904 (Volume 559)
  - (N-Z), July 1904 (Volume 560)
  - (A-E), August 1904 (Volume 561)
  - (F-M), August 1904 (Volume 562)
  - (N-Z), August 1904 (Volume 563)
  - (A-E), Sept 1904 (Volume 564)
  - (F-M), Sept 1904 (Volume 565)
  - (N-Z), Sept 1904 (Volume 566)
  - (A-E), Oct 1904 (Volume 567)
  - (F-M), Oct 1904 (Volume 568)
  - (N-Z), Oct 1904 (Volume 569)
  - (A-E), Nov 1904 (Volume 570)
  - (F-M), Nov 1904 (Volume 571)
  - (N-Z), Nov 1904 (Volume 572)
  - (A-E), Dec 1904 (Volume 573)
  - (F-M), Dec 1904 (Volume 574)
  - (N-Z), Dec 1904 (Volume 575)
  - (A-E), Jan 1905 (Volume 576)
  - (F-M), Jan 1905 (Volume 577)
  - (N-Z), Jan 1905 (Volume 578)
  - (A-E), Feb 1905 (Volume 579)
  - (F-M), Feb 1905 (Volume 580)
  - (N-Z), Feb 1905 (Volume 581)
  - (A-E), Mar 1905 (Volume 582)
  - (F-M), Mar 1905 (Volume 583)
  - (N-Z), Mar 1905 (Volume 584)
  - (A-E), April 1905 (Volume 585)
  - (F-M), April 1905 (Volume 586)
  - (N-Z), April 1905 (Volume 587)
  - (A-E), May 1905 (Volume 588)
  - (F-M), May 1905 (Volume 589)
  - (N-Z), May 1905 (Volume 590)
  - (A-E), June 1905 (Volume 591)
  - (F-M), June 1905 (Volume 592)
  - (N-Z), June 1905 (Volume 593)
  - Balance Sheet (A-E), July 1905 (Volume 594)
  - (F-M), July 1905 (Volume 595)
  - (N-Z), July 1905 (Volume 596)
  - (A-E), August 1905 (Volume 597)
  - (F-M), August 1905 (Volume 598)
  - (N-Z), August 1905 (Volume 599)
  - (A-E), Sept 1905 (Volume 600)
  - (F-M), Sept 1905 (Volume 601)
  - (N-Z), Sept 1905 (Volume 602)
  - (A-E), Oct 1905 (Volume 603)
  - (F-M), Oct 1905 (Volume 604)
  - (N-Z), Oct 1905 (Volume 605)
  - (A-E), Nov 1905 (Volume 606)
  - (F-M), Nov 1905 (Volume 607)
  - (N-Z), Nov 1905 (Volume 608)
  - (A-E), Dec 1905 (Volume 609)
  - (F-M), Dec 1905 (Volume 610)
  - (A-E), Jan 1906 (Volume 611)
  - (F-M), Jan 1906 (Volume 612)
  - (N-Z), Jan 1906 (Volume 613)
  - (A-E), Feb 1906 (Volume 614)
  - (F-M), Feb 1906 (Volume 615)
  - (N-Z), Feb 1906 (Volume 616)
  - (A-E), March 1906 (Volume 617)
  - (F-M), March 1906 (Volume 618)
  - (N-Z), March 1906 (Volume 619)
  - (A-E), April 1906 (Volume 620)
  - (F-M), April 1906 (Volume 621)
  - (N-Z), April 1906 (Volume 622)
  - (A-E), June 1906 (Volume 623)
  - (F-M), June 1906 (Volume 624)
  - (N-Z), June 1906 (Volume 625)
  - (A-E), July 1906 (Volume 626)
  - (F-M), July 1906 (Volume 627)
  - (N-Z), July 1906 (Volume 628)
  - (A-E), August 1906 (Volume 629)
  - (F-M), August 1906 (Volume 630)
  - (N-Z), August 1906 (Volume 631)
  - (A-E), Sept 1906 (Volume 632)
  - (F-M), Sept 1906 (Volume 633)
  - (N-Z), Sept 1906 (Volume 634)
  - (A-E), Oct 1906 (Volume 635)
  - (F-M), Oct 1906 (Volume 636)
  - (N-Z), Oct 1906 (Volume 637)
  - (A-E), Nov 1906 (Volume 638)
  - (F-M), Nov 1906 (Volume 639)
  - (N-Z), Nov 1906 (Volume 640)
  - (A-E), Dec 1906 (Volume 641)
  - (F-M), Dec 1906 (Volume 642)
  - (N-Z), Dec 1906 (Volume 643)
  - Special Accounts for, May 1906 (Volume 644)
  - (A-E), Jan 1907 (Volume 645)
  - (F-M), Jan 1907 (Volume 646)
  - (N-Z), Jan 1907 (Volume 647)
  - Balance Sheet (A-E), Feb 1907 (Volume 648)
  - (F-M), Feb 1907 (Volume 649)
  - (N-Z), Feb 1907 (Volume 650)
  - (A-E), March 1907 (Volume 651)
  - (F-M), March 1907 (Volume 652)
  - (N-Z), March 1907 (Volume 653)
  - (A-E), April 1907 (Volume 654)
  - (F-M), April 1907 (Volume 655)
  - (N-Z), April 1907 (Volume 656)
  - (A-E), May 1907 (Volume 657)
  - (F-M), May 1907 (Volume 658)
  - (N-Z), May 1907 (Volume 659)
  - (A-E), June 1907 (Volume 660)
  - (F-M), June 1907 (Volume 661)
  - (N-Z), June 1907 (Volume 662)
  - (A-E), July 1907 (Volume 663)
  - (F-M), July 1907 (Volume 664)
  - (N-Z), July 1907 (Volume 665)
  - (A-E), August 1907 (Volume 666)
  - (F-M), August 1907 (Volume 667)
  - (N-Z), August 1907 (Volume 668)
  - (A-E), Sept 1907 (Volume 669)
  - (F-M), Sept 1907 (Volume 670)
  - (N-Z), Sept 1907 (Volume 671)
  - (A-E), Oct 1907 (Volume 672)
  - (F-M), Oct 1907 (Volume 673)
  - (N-Z), Oct 1907 (Volume 674)
  - (A-E), Nov 1907 (Volume 675)
  - (F-M), Nov 1907 (Volume 676)
  - (N-Z), Nov 1907 (Volume 677)
  - (A-E), Dec 1907 (Volume 678)
  - (F-M), Dec 1907 (Volume 679)
  - (N-Z), Dec 1907 (Volume 680)
  - (A-E), Jan 1908 (Volume 681)
  - (F-M), Jan 1908 (Volume 682)
  - (N-Z), Jan 1908 (Volume 683)
  - (A-E), Feb 1908 (Volume 684)
  - (F-M), Feb 1908 (Volume 685)
  - (N-Z), Feb 1908 (Volume 686)
  - (A-E), March 1908 (Volume 687)
  - (F-M), March 1908 (Volume 688)
  - (N-Z), March 1908 (Volume 689)
  - (A-E), April 1908 (Volume 690)
  - (F-M), April 1908 (Volume 691)
  - (N-Z), April 1908 (Volume 692)
  - (A-E), May 1908 (Volume 693)
  - (F-M), May 1908 (Volume 694)
  - (N-Z), May 1908 (Volume 695)
  - (A-E), June 1908 (Volume 696)
  - (F-M), June 1908 (Volume 697)
  - (N-Z), June 1908 (Volume 698)
  - Balance Sheet (A-E), July 1908 (Volume 699)
  - (F-M), July 1908 (Volume 700)
  - (N-Z), July 1908 (Volume 701)
  - (A-E), August 1908 (Volume 702)
  - (F-M), August 1908 (Volume 703)
  - (N-Z), August 1908 (Volume 704)
  - (A-E), Sept 1908 (Volume 705)
  - (F-M), Sept 1908 (Volume 706)
  - (N-Z), Sept 1908 (Volume 707)
  - (A-E), Oct 1908 (Volume 708)
  - (F-M), Oct 1908 (Volume 709)
  - (N-Z), Oct 1908 (Volume 710)
  - (A-E), Nov 1908 (Volume 711)
  - (F-M), Nov 1908 (Volume 712)
  - (N-Z), Nov 1908 (Volume 713)
  - (A-E), Dec 1908 (Volume 714)
  - (F-M), Dec 1908 (Volume 715)
  - (N-Z), Dec 1908 (Volume 716)
  - (A-E), Jan 1909 (Volume 717)
  - (F-M), Jan 1909 (Volume 718)
  - (N-Z), Jan 1909 (Volume 719)
  - (A-E), Feb 1909 (Volume 720)
  - (F-M), Feb 1909 (Volume 721)
  - (N-Z), Feb 1909 (Volume 722)
  - (A-E), March 1909 (Volume 723)
  - (F-M), March 1909 (Volume 724)
  - (N-Z), March 1909 (Volume 725)
  - (A-E), April 1909 (Volume 726)
  - (F-M), April 1909 (Volume 727)
  - (N-Z), April 1909 (Volume 728)
  - (A-E), May 1909 (Volume 729)
  - (F-M), May 1909 (Volume 730)
  - (N-Z), May 1909 (Volume 731)
  - (A-E), June 1909 (Volume 732)
  - (F-M), June 1909 (Volume 733)
  - (N-Z), June 1909 (Volume 734)
  - (A-E), July 1909 (Volume 735)
  - (F-M), July 1909 (Volume 736)
  - (N-Z), July 1909 (Volume 737)
  - (A-E), August 1909 (Volume 738)
  - (F-M), August 1909 (Volume 739)
  - (N-Z), August 1909 (Volume 740)
  - (A-E), Sept 1909 (Volume 741)
  - (F-M), Sept 1909 (Volume 742)
  - (N-Z), Sept 1909 (Volume 743)
  - (A-E), Oct 1909 (Volume 744)
  - (F-M), Oct 1909 (Volume 745)
  - (N-Z), Oct 1909 (Volume 746)
  - (A-E), Nov 1909 (Volume 747)
  - (F-M), Nov 1909 (Volume 748)
  - (N-Z), Nov 1909 (Volume 749)
  - (A-E), Dec 1909 (Volume 750)
  - (F-M), Dec 1909 (Volume 751)
  - (N-Z), Dec 1909 (Volume 752)
  - Balance Sheet (A-E), Jan 1910 (Volume 753)
  - (F-M), Jan 1910 (Volume 754)
  - (N-Z), Jan 1910 (Volume 755)
  - (A-E), Feb 1910 (Volume 756)
  - (F-M), Feb 1910 (Volume 757)
  - (N-Z), Feb 1910 (Volume 578)
  - (A-E), March 1910 (Volume 759)
  - (F-M), March 1910 (Volume 760)
  - (N-Z), March 1910 (Volume 761)
  - (A-E), April 1910 (Volume 762)
  - (F-M), April 1910 (Volume 763)
  - (N-Z), April 1910 (Volume 764)
  - (A-E), May 1910 (Volume 765)
  - (F-M), May 1910 (Volume 766)
  - (N-Z), May 1910 (Volume 767)
  - (A-E), June 1910 (Volume 768)
  - (F-M), June 1910 (Volume 769)
  - (N-Z), June 1910 (Volume 770)
  - (A-E), July 1910 (Volume 771)
  - (F-M), July 1910 (Volume 772)
  - (N-Z), July 1910 (Volume 773)
  - (A-E), August 1910 (Volume 774)
  - (F-M), August 1910 (Volume 775)
  - (N-Z), August 1910 (Volume 776)
  - (A-E), Sept 1910 (Volume 777)
  - (F-M), Sept 1910 (Volume 778)
  - (N-Z), Sept 1910 (Volume 779)
  - (A-E), Oct 1910 (Volume 780)
  - (F-M), Oct 1910 (Volume 781)
  - (N-Z), Oct 1910 (Volume 782)
  - (A-E), Nov 1910 (Volume 783)
  - (F-M), Nov 1910 (Volume 784)
  - (N-Z), Nov 1910 (Volume 785)
  - (A-E), Dec 1910 (Volume 786)
  - (F-M), Dec 1910 (Volume 787)
  - (N-Z), Dec 1910 (Volume 788)
  - (A-E), Jan 1911 (Volume 789)
  - (F-M), Jan 1911 (Volume 790)
  - (N-Z), Jan 1911 (Volume 791)
  - (A-E), Feb 1911 (Volume 792)
  - (F-M), Feb 1911 (Volume 793)
  - (N-Z), Feb 1911 (Volume 794)
  - (A-E), March 1911 (Volume 795)
  - (F-M), March 1911 (Volume 796)
  - (N-Z), March 1911 (Volume 797)
  - (A-E), April 1911 (Volume 798)
  - (F-M), April 1911 (Volume 799)
  - (N-Z), April 1911 (Volume 800)
  - (A-E), May 1911 (Volume 801)
  - (F-M), May 1911 (Volume 802)
  - (N-Z), May 1911 (Volume 803)
  - (A-E), June 1911 (Volume 804)
  - (F-M), June 1911 (Volume 805)
  - (N-Z), June 1911 (Volume 806)
  - Balance Sheet (A-E), July 1911 (Volume 807)
  - (F-M), July 1911 (Volume 808)
  - (N-Z), July 1911 (Volume 809)
  - (A-E), August 1911 (Volume 810)
  - (F-M), August 1911 (Volume 811)
  - (N-Z), August 1911 (Volume 812)
  - (A-E), Sept 1911 (Volume 813)
  - (F-M), Sept 1911 (Volume 814)
  - (N-Z), Sept 1911 (Volume 815)
  - (A-E), Oct 1911 (Volume 816)
  - (F-M), Oct 1911 (Volume 817)
  - (N-Z), Oct 1911 (Volume 818)
  - (A-E), Nov 1911 (Volume 819)
  - (F-M), Nov 1911 (Volume 820)
  - (N-Z), Nov 1911 (Volume 821)
  - (A-E), Dec 1911 (Volume 822)
  - (F-M), Dec 1911 (Volume 823)
  - (N-Z), Dec 1911 (Volume 824)
  - Record of Promissory Notes, 1864-1872 (Volume 825)
  - Stock Book, 1872-1881 (Volume 825a)
  - Stock Book, 1891 (Volume 826)
  - Orders for Purchase and Sale of Stocks, 1865-1895 (Volume 827)
  - [UNK] letter Copying Book, 1899 (Volume 827a)
  - Release of Liability Book, 1883-1900 (Volume 828)
  - J.A. Donohoe in account with Donohoe, Kelly Banking Co., 1863-1905 (Volume 829)
  - Ledger, [1886?]
  - Record of checks, 1896-1899
  - Record of checks, 1898-1906
  - Accounts, 1906
  - Accounts, 1906-1908
  - Tables of Exchange
  - Cash, 1914-1915
  - Hemme and Long Piano Manufacturing Co. (Volume 830)
  - By laws, 1880
  - Minutes, 1880-1881
  - Stock Certificates
- Series C. General Ledger Vouchers
  - General Ledger Vouchers, 1906-1907 (Volume 831)
  - General Ledger Vouchers, 1908-August 1909 (Volume 832)
  - General Ledger Vouchers, Sept 1909-1910 (Volume 833)
  - General Ledger Vouchers, 1911-June 1912 (Volume 834)
  - General Ledger Vouchers, July 1912-Nov. 1913 (Volume 835)
  - General Ledger Vouchers, Dec 1913-April 1915 (Volume 836)
  - General Ledger Vouchers, May 1915-August 1916 (Volume 837)
  - General Ledger Vouchers, Sept 1916-1917 (Volume 838)